- Now with a Ray
Bloch background,
The Supremes open with
"You Can't Hurry Love",
and then go on to a medley
of their big hit songs.
So let's have a fine
welcome for The Supremes.
(crowd cheers)
(upbeat music starts)
♪ I need love, love ♪
♪ To ease my mind ♪
♪ And I need to find, find ♪
♪ Someone to call mine ♪
♪ But mama said ♪
♪ You can't hurry love ♪
♪ No, you'll just have to wait ♪
♪ She said love
don't come easy ♪
♪ It's a game of give and take ♪
♪ You can't hurry love ♪
♪ No, you'll just have to wait ♪
♪ She said trust, give it time ♪
♪ No matter how long it takes ♪
♪ But how many heartaches
must I stand? ♪
♪ Before I find the love
to let me live again ♪
♪ Right now the only thing
that keeps me hanging on ♪
♪ When I feel my strength,
yeah, it's almost gone ♪
♪ I remember mama said ♪
♪ (You can't hurry love) ♪
♪ No you'll just have to wait ♪
♪ She said love
don't come easy ♪
♪ It's a game of give and take ♪
♪ How long must I wait? ♪
♪ How much more can I take? ♪
♪ Before loneliness ♪
♪ Will cause my heart,
heart to break ♪
♪ No, I can't bear to
live my life alone ♪
♪ I grow impatient for
a love to call my own ♪
♪ But when I feel that
I, I can't go on ♪
♪ These precious words
keep me hanging on ♪
♪ I remember mama said ♪
♪ (You can't hurry love) ♪
♪ No, you'll just have to wait ♪
♪ She said love
don't come easy ♪
♪ It's a game of give and take ♪
♪ You can't hurry love ♪
♪ No, you'll just have to wait ♪
♪ She said love
don't come easy ♪
♪ It's a game of give
and take, now break! ♪
♪ Now love, love
don't come easy ♪
♪ But I keep on waiting ♪
♪ Anticipating for
that soft voice ♪
♪ To talk to me at night ♪
♪ For some tender arms ♪
♪ To hold me tight ♪
♪ I keep waiting ♪
♪You gotta give and take ♪
♪ But it ain't easy ♪
(Love don't come easy) ♪
♪ It ain't easy ♪
♪ But mama said ♪
♪ You can't hurry love ♪
♪ No, you'll just have to wait ♪
♪ She said love
don't come easy ♪
♪ It's a game of give and take ♪
♪ You can't hurry love ♪
♪ No, you'll just have to wait ♪
♪ She said trust, give it time ♪
♪ No matter how long it takes ♪
♪ You can't ♪
♪ Hurry ♪
♪ Love ♪
(audience applauding)